# Vasile Fana

• 5A Stork Road, London, E7 9HR (United Kingdom)

London, 21 August 2016 Letter of intent

Dear To whom it may concern,

I am 23 year old Computer Engineer graduate from Romania.

I have a background in web development and successfully designing a websites layout, usability and appearance. Over the last few years, I've had the opportunity of working for several school projects and individual projects, this has given me extensive web designing knowledge and technical skills.

I strongly believe that my background experience that I have in Computer systems it will help me to better understand the whole picture of your working environment and it will allow me to focus on details that are most important for the business. I am coming from a place where Information Technology holds the first place in the country economy and this keeps me motivated and gives me the opportunity to stay updated with all new upcoming technologies.

I hope you will give me the chance to prove my abilities and to be a part of your business team. Thank You.

Yours sincerely,

Vasile Fana

Enclosed: Curriculum vitae, Language passport

# PERSONAL INFORMATION

# Vasile Fana



- 5A Stork Road, London, E7 9HR (United Kingdom)
- 07522109202
- vaseafana@gmail.com
- vasilefana.github.io
- Skype vasyok72

Sex Male | Date of birth 4 Apr 1993 | Nationality Moldovian, Romanian

#### PERSONAL STATEMENT

A graduate IT engineer, motivated and with a willingness to learn.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### 1 Nov 2015-Present

#### Free Lancer

 Creating web pages using: HTML5/CSS3/jQuery/Bootstrap/JavaScript/Wordpress/Ruby on Rails/Drupal

## 15 May 2009-Present

# Computer Technician

self-employed

- Examine and repair computer hardware and peripheral components.
- Test functionality and assess problems by operating computer systems or related.
- Troubleshoot computer systems problems.
- Take apart and re-assemble computer components and parts.
- Use small handheld tools such as screwdrivers, voltmeters, etc.
- Manually set up computer systems and hardware, and install or re-install software programs for computer users.
- Work with colleagues to resolve computer-related problems.
- Explain computer malfunction issues to customers.

# 15 Feb 2015-30 May 2015

# **Technical Support Specialist**

Velvet com S.R.L.

Panseleleor 5, Bacau (Romania)

# www.velvetcom.ro

- Assisting customers with their technical problems;
- Installing and maintain the SmartCash and Freya programs.
- Installing scales and calibrate them, connect the scales with exiting database add/or connect with portable scanners.

#### 30 Jun 2013-30 Oct 2015

## Work & Travel

Wequassett Resort and Golf club/Chatham Bars Inn, East Harwich (United States)

- I have participated in the Work and Travel USA program for the last three summers, I have accumulated a lot of experience working with high motivated people,in a big business environment such as 4 diamond resort and 5 star resort.
- I have learned to be a great problem solver, a team player and a positive person at all time.

# **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**





#### 1 Oct 2012-30 Jun 2016

# Information Technologies Engineer

CGPA: 8 93/10

University Vasile Alecsandri

Calea Mărășești 158, Bacau (Romania)

www.ub.ro

Graduating this four year university as an IT engineer, I have gained strong coding skills and also good knowledges of the computer systems and network systems.

## 1 Mar 2016-9 Mar 2016

## Erasmus+

Uludağ Üniversitesi, Bursa (Turkey)

■ I have participate in this training program called "Encode your dreams" where I gained new coding skills, and it was also a good exchange experience interacting with students form Italy, Ukraine, Lithuania and Turkey.

### 20 Apr 2015-30 Jun 2016

# Technical support

Level 1

Magister software, Bucharest (Romania)

- Providing necessary help in different situations in a professional manner.
- Debug and repair broken parts of the technical equipment.
- Installing network equipment, configure POS devices and connect them to a local server.

## PERSONAL SKILLS

## Mother tongue(s)

#### Romanian

# Other language(s)

UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
Listening	Reading	Spoken interaction	Spoken production	
C1	B2	C1	B2	B1
C2	C2	C2	C2	C1

Russian English

> Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user - B1 and B2: Independent user - C1 and C2: Proficient user Common European Framework of Reference for Languages

# Organisational / managerial skills

- I have always been a productive team player. I always played in team sports such as soccer and basketball and always performed as captain. Therefore I have excellent leadership skills.
- I also was a team leader in a Erasmus+ project having best results and taking a good care of my team mates.

#### Job-related skills

- excellent problem-solving skills
- a willingness to work flexibly but in an organized manner
- the ability to follow exact instructions
- the ability to work to deadlines
- a commitment to keep up to date with technology
- the ability to work alone or as part of a team
- creative skills to turn clients' ideas into workable plans

# Digital competence

# (1 for beginner and 5 to professional)

Windows XP, Vista,7,8.1,10 ,OS X El Capitan(5)

C/C++, Java (2), MySQL (3), C# (2), PHP(2)Solid Edge (3)CISCO Routers (3), TCP/IP (4), cabling skills (5)HTML5 (3), CSS3 (3), Bootstrap (2), JavaScript (2), Ruby on Rails (2)



Driving licence B